我滴天啊
大家  看看这场面 大家转身看看这一切
在继续之前 我想说
我们很感激 非常感谢大家 我们很感动
非常开心和荣幸能在这里演出
感谢大家 接下来将演唱第一张专辑的歌“太阳”  希望你们喜欢
说：一 二 和 三  开始
After school Walking home
放学后走在回家的路上
Fresh dirt under my fingernails
新鲜的泥土还留在我的指甲中
I can smell hot asphalt
我仿佛可以闻到热沥青的味道
Cars screech to a halt to let me pass
汽车都停了下来给我让路
And I cannot remember
我不记得
What life was like through photographs
照片中的我当时是怎样生活的
Trying to recreate images life gives us from our past
我一直在尝试回到过去的生活中去
And sometimes it's a sad song
有时它是一曲悲歌
But I cannot forget
但是我不能忘却
Refuse to regret So glad I met you
拒绝遗憾痛惜 遇见你我很快乐
Take my breath away
请带走我的呼吸
Make everyday
让每一天
Worth all of the pain that I've gone through
曾经受到的伤害对我来说都是值得的
And mama I've been cryin'
妈妈我曾经哭的那样伤心
Cause things ain't how they used to be
因为仿佛所有的事情都和从前不同了
She said, the battle's almost won
妈妈说：乌云总会过去的
And we're only several miles from the sun
其实阳光就在离我们不远的地方
Moving on down my street
顺着街道前行
I see people I won't ever meet
许多陌生人和我擦肩而过
I think of her, take a breath
我想着她 深呼吸
Feel the beat in the rhythm of my steps
感觉好像有什么东西打乱了我的节奏
And sometimes its a sad song
有时它就如一首悲歌
But I cannot forget
但我无法忘却
Refuse to regret
拒绝遗憾
So glad I met you
很高兴遇见你
Take my breath away
请带走我的呼吸
Make everyday
让每一天
Worth all of the pain that I've gone through
曾经受到的伤害对我来说都是值得的
And mama I've been cryin'
妈妈我曾经哭的那样伤心
Cause things ain't how they used to be
因为仿佛所有的事情都和从前不同了
She said, the battle's almost won
妈妈说：乌云总会过去的
And we're only several miles from the sun
其实阳光就在离我们不远的地方
I can feel severa,I can feel the warm
我能感受到太阳到来的温暖
女士们，先生们  在另一边有请詹姆斯为我们演奏吉他
The rhythm of the conversation
甜美的声音
The perfection of her creation
是她完美的创造
The sex she slipped into my coffee
那熟悉的场景出现在我的脑海中
The way she felt when she first saw me
那是当我们第一次相遇时
Hate to love and love to hate her
不想再去爱了 但却因此爱上了恨
Like a broken record player
如同一个老旧了的唱机一样
Back and forth and here and gone
翻来覆去
and on and on and on and on
一直这样下去
But I cannot forget
但我无法忘却
Refuse to regret
拒绝遗憾
So glad I met you
很高兴遇见你
Take my breath away
请带走我的呼吸
Make everyday
让每一天
Worth all of the pain that I've gone through
曾经受到的伤害对我来说都是值得的
And mama I've been cryin'
妈妈我曾经哭的那样伤心
Cause things ain't how they used to be
因为仿佛所有的事情都和从前不同了
She said, the battle's almost won
妈妈说：乌云总会过去的
And we're only several miles
其实阳光就在离我们不远的地方
said, the battle's almost won
妈妈说：乌云总会过去的
And we're only several miles form the sun
其实阳光就在离我们不远的地方
谢谢大家